5 days for me to set up 1 deal.
the time has come for me to grow as a business,
as a company too,
because I'm not being able to handle the orders.
a look
how are the orders from the workshop of the real
it's not good at all,
but if I don't solve
remains a problem.
guess where I'm going?
Did you like my Brigadier and want to exchange an idea with me?
face, ah,
if it doesn't work out no,
I already have.
bro, what will change?
leave the toolbox in the car to
talk to the owner?
man,
there,
there.
thank you
girls of heart,
have you seen?
Iki tane saçlarım var.
the company has to be rich
and the citizen has to be poor.
press again in your company
until she grew up,
it doesn't stay.
oh,
I buy it,
I buy that,
I'm going to buy this,
will not buy anything.
your company has to be
leader blur,
then he on the fish,
an eye on the cat.
I will do what?
I will try more commercial points,
I don't know,
make 1 partnership,
put the letters like this.
Wow,
still the guy gives me a deal in the beard.
bro,
thirty little box,
thirty closed.
huh? bro,
all good for you!
I think I managed to put together a business,
it's too high
you don't have to invest in structure
to be able to serve everyone.
increase your product ticket.
guess what I'm going to do?
investing more again.